ethioscoop.com 2016-10-21

# Privacy Policy - EthioScoop.com

## Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement for EthioScoop

EthioScoop has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: EthioScoop 

## Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site, and to help identify you and your shopping cart. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, and for other purposes.

Our Site uses cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies for other purposes.

## Advertisers

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.

## Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

This site contains links to other sites. EthioScoop is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Children's Guidelines

EthioScoop is a family oriented website and as such due caution is taken to see that it meets with all national, international and local standards of operation. Safeguarding the Personal Information of children is extremely important. For those AmharicMovies sites specifically directed at children, and where users have indicated they are younger than 18, EthioScoop sites will collect the minimum amount of Personal Information necessary to the operation of the service. These EthioScoop  sites will also send follow up mail to the user's e-mail address instructing them to seek parental permission for their use of the site. A child's Personal Information will be used for the operation of the service but it will not be used for "Secondary Uses" without a parent's permission.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit www.networkadvertising.org.

EthioScoop.com works with third parties that serves ads to this site.

Send mail to info at EthioScoop.com with questions or comments about this web site.
